Zhou Rong is not playing tricks.
How so?
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
20 million.
They can't get that much
from the bank this early.
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
They can only find people
to scrape it together.
♪ Oh, gimme ♪
These people are all here
to deliver money.
♪ Dance me in the richness ♪
♪ Raining, make it rain ♪
♪ Oh, cash is my revolution ♪
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 22]
[Sanjiangkou People's Hospital]
You stay here and keep watch.
Don't let anyone get close.
Yes, sir.
Who is it?
Wh-What are you doing?
I didn't do anything illegal.
Chief Zhang.
I was fast asleep.
My heart is racing from the shock.
What's going on, Captain Wang?
You...
Me?
Yes, you.
We found a set of bianzhong.
Does it have anything to do with you?
No.
Really.
I'm not interested in that kind of stuff.
Really, Chief Zhang.
I'm not into that kind of thing.
Really, Captain Wang.
"Zhong"—the end—
signifies bad luck after all.
Makes sense.
Get some rest.
Watch what you're doing.
Chief Zhang!
You can't treat me like this!
Am I dreaming?
[First Inpatient Department]
Turn off all the headlights.
Be quiet.
Don't disturb the people resting.
Get in the car.
[First Inpatient Department]
Chief Zhang.
What are we here for?
To make Zhou Rong suspect Lang Bowen.
I thought so too before.
But...
Haven't we used this trick before?
How many times have we used it?
Three times.
You think
all is fair in war.
Exactly because we've used it—
and we used it 3 times—
Zhou Rong is very likely
to have anticipated what we anticipated.
But he won't anticipate
that we anticipated his anticipation.
Zhou Rong is about to make a move?
[Police]
Rong...
[Come on—What if it's funny?]
[Health and longevity]
Dad.
Mom.
I am unfilial.
This parting...
Old man.
They say you raise a son
so they can
take care of you in your old age.
Have our son drive back
and take you to see the doctor,
okay?
No need.
He works in a big company.
He's very busy.
Let's...
Let's not cause him trouble.
This is a million US dollars...
Dad.
I'm back.
You're coughing so badly.
Why don't you go to the hospital?
I'll go buy you some cough syrup.
[Lower your head]
Hello?
Ren?
The money's ready?
The money is in the car.
You can count it.
Let's go.
Mr. Zhou, take your medicine first.
Here.
There's one more thing.
What?
Zhang Yi'ang went to the hospital
to see Lang Bowen last night.
What did they talk about?
I'm not sure.
I heard the hallway
was guarded by the police.
Only Zhang Yi'ang
and Wang Ruijun went into the room.
They left without saying much.
Also, Du Cong
just called.
He said
they found Li Penggai's car,
and the money is in it.
Okay.
Tell them all to come!
It's Li Penggai, right?
Gai, what happened?
I'm fine.
Open the small gate for me.
Okay.
Lock it up.
Good.
Li Penggai just went inside.
This is going to be a good show.
Mr. Zhou.
Ren.
They snatched
the money?
They stole the car too?
According to you,
those two junk collectors are just losers.
You had a knife on you,
yet you got knocked out
and got your money and car stolen.
Do you think anyone would believe that?
Think I'm a fool,
huh?
No, no. I...
I-I remember now.
I remember.
It wasn't them. It wasn't them.
Then who was it?
Well...
When it happened,
one of them was on this side of me,
and the other was on this side.
It wasn't them.
There must be someone else.
There has to be another person!
So you're saying,
with your skills,
you didn't even notice
that there was someone else
in such a small space?
He's an expert.
Super fast too.
I couldn't even react
before I was knocked out.
So they have the phone?
P-Probably.
It was when I asked them
for the phone
that I was ambushed.
Ren.
Can we trust what Li Penggai said?
I trust him.
Why?
One million dollars.
Because he knows what will happen to him
if he takes your money.
I took my medicine, right?
Okay.
Those two junk collectors
took my phone.
Then those two who robbed me—
why do they still want to
make a deal with me?
They want to kidnap me?
Besides, who could knock him out
with just one strike?
Who is his boss,
and what do they want?
Hello?
Hello, Mr. Zhou.
I thought about it.
Twenty million is too much.
It's appropriate for us,
but not for you.
How about this?
Five million.
10 o'clock.
Put it in the trash can
at Sculpture Square.
How's that?
Sure.
Make sure you come and get it.
Rong.
Those two boys are showing mercy.
They said 20 million is too much,
and lowered it to 5 million.
Put it in the trash can
at Sculpture Square
at 10 o'clock.
Mr. Zhou,
this doesn't feel right.
Let's cancel the deal.
Cancel what?
Since they want to play,
I'll play a big game with them.
Drive.
[Sanjiangkou People's Hospital]
What time's lunch?
Bowen,
it's still early.
Go order some fruit.
What are you mulling over now?
Let me sort it out for you.
Bro,
how can you still eat?
If Mr. Zhou doesn't contact us,
can't we just ask him
if he found the phone or not?
Why do I feel like
you are my boss?
Boss, here.
Have some nuts.
Do you think the fruit is for you?
Zhou Rong will be here soon.
Bowen, Mr. Zhou is here.
Let him in.
Mr. Zhou.
Jianren.
Ren.
Sit.
Well,
I had someone order some fruit.
What do you want to eat?
What's all this?
I came to see you.
Of course I should be the one
buying things.
How could I let you buy anything?
I brought everything.
Jianren, give me a back rub.
Pound my back!
Yangyang.
You go out first.
Mr. Zhou and I have business to discuss.
Don't leave, Yangyang.
You are not a kid anymore.
You should care about family matters.
Sit down.
Mr. Zhou.
You seem quite angry.
Is it because of
Zhang Yi'ang's visit last night?
Can you explain that
clearly to me?
If I could explain this clearly,
then Zhang Yi'ang
would be too incompetent.
If I told you
he came here last night
making a big scene
but told me nothing—
just wants you to make me doubt you
and cause internal friction—
would you believe that?
Mr. Zhou,
what will it take
for you to believe me?
In 1944,
on the Western Front in Europe,
20 German divisions besieged the Ardennes.
8,000 American soldiers surrendered.
But the 101st Airborne Division
held the line.
In the end,
the Allies won the victory.
Now I am Eisenhower.
Are you willing
to be my 101st Airborne Division?
You know about the battle
of the back mountain, right?
Whose back mountain?
Those 2 guys who snatched the phone
are now asking for 5 million
to redeem the phone.
They asked me to drop
the money at 10 o'clock today...
Sculpture Square.
In the trash can at Sculpture Square.
They will return the phone
when they see the money.
Coincidentally,
Zhu Yifei asked me
to trade the bianzhong today.
So I was hoping
you could help me run
the phone deal errand.
I have the money ready.
As for those two,
do whatever you want.
But the phone,
you must get it back.
If my leg were fine,
I would definitely go.
That's why I had Yangyang
stay, didn't I?
Mr. Zhou.
I can go in his stead.
Shut up.
What?
I can't go, and you can't go—
can't Yangyang go?
Don't want the phone anymore?
Bowen.
You don't care
about this phone at all?
I do care. I care a lot.
But we can't let Yangyang go.
Then who else can go?
Who?
Who else?
I can just give up this phone.
At worst, I'll move somewhere else
and still make a fortune.
But I won't.
I want those bastards to know
that no one can touch my money.
Whoever lays a finger on it,
I'll fight them to the death.
That's my principle.
Look at you.
What have you become?
Are you still the dominating
Bowen?
It's obvious
that someone is targeting us.
Why are you too scared to step up?
Hiding is useless.
If you're done for
and I'm done for,
will Yangyang be fine?
You have quite a few enemies, right?
Without protection,
what will happen to Yangyang?
Bowen,
I think
you should let Yangyang take a chance.
Give him an opportunity
to surprise us all.
How's that?
Bro,
let me go.
Get ready to work.
Yangyang,
I'll wait for you downstairs.
Remember this,
leave no survivors.
Okay.
What about you?
Why?
Do you think another team will pop up
and attack me from behind?
Come here.
Are you stupid?
Huh?
I know
you want to drive Zhou Rong away.
But now is not the time.
That phone is
more important to you than
it is to Zhou Rong.
You don't know shit!
Not to mention the phone
falling into the hands of the police,
even if it's on the national news,
I wouldn't be afraid.
Why?
Because I didn't kill Lu Zheng.
He was hit by a car.
When I was following him,
the phone happened to record
the moment he was hit—
what a coincidence!
I showed the video to Zhou Rong,
saying I did
exactly what he wanted
just to get money from him.
It had absolutely nothing
to do with us in the first place.
If Zhou Rong ran away in fear,
Sanjiangkou would be ours.
It's a great thing.
Now he's forcing me to kill someone.
He couldn't do anything to me before.
But look at you—
you agreed to it.
What do we do now?
Go
a little further later.
Find a payphone
and call the police.
Whatever you do,
don't tell them who you are.
Tell the police
about the phone deal.
If the police catch those two first,
we'll be fine.
Do you hear me?
I can't do that.
Why?
Here,
take this.
Zhu Yifei has a gun too.
You keep it.
I have a way.
I'll take the stairs.
In the future,
don't make decisions on your own.
Ask me first.
The reason I'm your bro
isn't just because I am older.
Bowen.
Why are you the one going?
Are you up to it?
What else can we do?
I'm Number One after all.
You really are a good brother.
Give me your phone.
Charge it.
Use this one.
They will contact you.
Good luck.
Okay.
Lang Bowen is out.
We'll follow him.
You keep an eye on Zhou Rong.
Understood.
Hu Jianren drove away.
We'll follow him.
Team 2, cover the hospital for us.
Will this trick work?
Absolutely.
Tomorrow, I'll say
I've been coughing up blood lately.
I'll wear this vest inside
and go to the hospital for an X-ray.
Mr. Zhou will have to let me go
to the provincial capital
or Beijing for treatment.
Will he believe it?
It'll be a huge black patch on the lungs—
that's lung cancer.
I'm going to get lung cancer.
Ren?
I heard at the door
you're getting lung cancer.
I was just kidding.
Come in.
Here.
Ren, please have a seat.
Sit.
Turn around.
This is where your heart is.
This is a heart disease.
Mr. Zhou has already started
suspecting you.
Can you stop asking for
trouble?
What should I do then?
How can I make Mr. Zhou
stop suspecting me?
That's exactly why I'm here.
Last night, Zhu Yifei
called Mr. Zhou,
saying they'll trade the bianzhong today
and specifically asked Mr. Zhou
to go in person.
So,
Mr. Zhou is planning to take him out.
It's too dangerous
for Mr. Zhou to go alone.
How about
you go instead of him?
Ren,
well...
can he not go?
Shall I talk to Mr. Zhou
about this?
I'll go.
Yibo.
Yi...
Change your clothes.
What were you thinking?
Go find Lang Bowen
and ask him to help me.
Just tell him
I will definitely not tell anyone
about what happened
the night Ye Jian died.
Ask him to please help me.
Got it?
You can only tell him this.
Got it.
[Meal Times]
You just have to do the paperwork
at the inpatient department.
Thank you.
Yangyang!
Which room is your brother in?
Where is your brother?
Where is he?
What's the matter, Qi?
I am looking for him.
His phone is turned off.
My brother is not available right now.
Where is he? Tell me.
There's no time.
My brother went out on an errand.
If there's anything,
you can tell me, Qi.
Yibo is in trouble.
Only Bowen can help him.
When you see your brother, tell him...
Yibo will never tell anyone
what happened
on the night Ye Jian died.
Ask your brother to call Yibo.
B-But my brother won't be back
anytime soon.
Zhang.
Is putting all our attention
on Zhou Rong
and Lang Bowen
a good idea?
What's wrong with that?
When Fang Chao and Liu Zhi
were getting gas earlier,
they tried to pay in US dollars
but got rejected.
Then they went to a hotel
and paid the deposit in US dollars too.
Could it be that they don't have
any Chinese Yuan left on them?
So?
So they will definitely try
to get some money.
How?
How will they try to get money?
The phone.
They still have
that phone.
They will definitely find Zhou Rong
to strike a deal
with this phone for money.
So if we just
keep a close eye on Zhou Rong's gang,
we can catch these two.
Our current plan
is flawless.
Chief Zhang.
Speak.
Just received an anonymous tip
saying Zhou Rong has an
important deal today.
What kind of deal?
They didn't say.
But there's a deal.
Zhou Rong is quite busy, huh?
Keep a close eye on him.
See what he's up to today.
♪ The chance is waiting patiently
in the bowl ♪
♪ Who covered my eyes ♪
♪ I'm full of ideas ♪
Hello?
Put it in the trash can at the entrance.
Put the case
in those two trash cans.
Hurry.
All units, attention.
This is very likely
the location for the deal.
Bowen.
It won't fit.
Useless.
Lang Bowen got out of the car too.
Take that out,
and it'll fit, right?
The money is in the trash can
you mentioned.
Where's the phone?
I'm watching you.
Take the case out.
Put it in the trash can
at the entrance of Dahua Alley
in 10 minutes.
You only have 10 minutes.
Hello?
Take the case out.
Hurry up.
All units, attention.
This is not the location for the deal.
They're here.
I'll go.
Wait.
Hello?
In 20 minutes,
put it in the trash can at the entrance
of Huining Park.
Hello?
He's obsessed with trash cans.
Take the case out!
Get in the car!
Hurry!
Get in the car.
Okay.
Hello, Mr. Zhou.
Mr. Zhu.
What's going on now?
It's quite hot in the car.
You should have seen the money.
Can I take a look at
the bianzhong now?
The bianzhong is on the second floor.
It's not convenient
to move it back and forth.
How about, Mr. Zhou,
you come up and take a look yourself?
No way.
I am in the light and you are in the dark.
You want me to go up?
I am not a child.
Mr. Zhou, you are overthinking.
It really is inconvenient
to move it back and forth.
Then you have no sincerity.
Uncle.
I'll go.
Mr. Zhou!
Come down!
I'll take you up!
Mr. Zhou?
Bro.
[Police]
Get out! Quick!
Stop!
Put your hands up!
Hurry up!
Where is Zhou Rong?
Speak. Where is Zhou Rong?
I don't know!
Zhu Yifei is inside.
Cuff them!
Don't move when you get off later.
Don't move!
Get off!
Go!
Don't move!
Behave yourself.
♪ He is ♪
♪ Too cunning but like a joke ♪
♪ Ha ha ha ♪
♪ He ♪
♪ Wears his glamorous nails ♪
Let's split up for the search.
Okay
♪ Oh, he ♪
♪ A rusted flower etched
across his chest ♪
♪ Oh, he ♪
♪ Says your worldview's still too small ♪
♪ A rat that steals rice—
humans call it cunning ♪
♪ A human who steals honey—
calls the bees hardworking ♪
No.
♪ Absurd, greedy—
self-proclaimed superior beings ♪
♪ Hypocritical, wasteful, hollow—
this gaudy human race ♪
My car!
Stop!
What's going on?
Someone drove my car away!
♪ Ha ha ha ha ♪
There's no brake!
Stop right there!
♪ Ha ha ha ha ♪
♪ He is ♪
♪ Too cunning but like a joke ♪
♪ Ha ha ha ♪
♪ He ♪
♪ Wears his glamorous nails ♪
He's dead for sure.
Hello?
I'm at the park entrance.
Put the money in the trash can.
Which one?
Are you blind?
The one at the entrance.
There are two at the entrance.
The red one or the green one?
The green one.
Can you see me now?
Yes, we can.
Is it the one I'm pointing at?
That's the one.
Do you want the darn money or not?
Why are you making me go round and round!
He's quite ticked off.
I have a card
with 5 million for you.
Take the money and get out of Sanjiangkou.
Hello?
He hung up?
Bad guys nowadays
are so impolite.
Get off.
What is he doing?
Thinking of leaving again?
All units, attention.
Get ready to act any time.
Go.
Get off!
Out for a breather?
I'm going back to the hospital
to change my dressing.
Wh-What did I do?
Nothing.
Take him back to the station
to change his dressing.
Yes, sir.
Chief Zhang?
Chief Zhang!
Get off.
Wang,
what's the situation on your side?
We caught Hu Jianren and Lu Yibo.
The seller of the bianzhong is Zhu Yifei.
When he was trying to escape,
he fell down the mountain and died.
What about Zhou Rong?
Zhou Rong didn't come at all.
He probably went back to his villa.
We fell for a decoy.
The deal is very likely
taking place at Zhou Rong's villa.
Head to Zhou Rong's villa right away.
Chief Zhang!
You can't treat me like this!
You can't treat me like this,
Chief Zhang.
I just got discharged from the hospital.
How should I treat you, then?
Chief Zhang!
Captain Wang.
Huo Zheng got away.
Didn't he die?
He didn't die.
Chief Zhang.
Huo Zheng is not dead.
He got away.
Arrange a search first,
and then come over right away.
Copy that.
Take them away.
Get up!
Go!
Move!
Bro.
Do we make a move?
Let's wait a little longer.
Mr. Zhou.
Where did you find it?
In a small alley
not far from the company.
I found it on my way to work just now.
The car wasn't locked
and the keys were still in the ignition,
so I drove it back.
You didn't sleep all night, did you?
This car has a GPS tracker.
It hasn't stopped since yesterday.
It almost drove out of Sanjiangkou.
So how did you find it
in a small alley?
You've been undercover
next to me for so many years.
I didn't expect it to be you.
Wait.
Don't do it here.